<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="@color/white"
    tools:context=".Help">

    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintHorizontal_bias="0.5"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent">

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/textHelp"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:paddingBottom="20dp"
            android:paddingLeft="25dp"
            android:paddingRight="25dp"
            android:paddingTop="20dp"
            android:text="1. Users can sign up with email verification in order to get their statistics (i.e. number of games won, number of games lost, etc) saved when they play the game while signed in.\n\n2. While signing up, users may choose to upload a profile picture or they may choose to skip the uploading of profile picture. If a user chooses to skip the uploading of profile picture, then a default picture serves as the user’s profile picture. (However, users may upload a profile picture later, by editing thier profile).\n\n3. While signing up, users cannot use an email id which is already present in the database, thus,email id is unique for every user.\n\n4. Users sign in by entering their email id and password.\n\n5. When signed in, users can play against an intelligent computer. To play against the intelligent computer, the users have to enter turn choice (i.e, whether the user should start the game or the computer should start the game).In the game against the intelligent computer, if the users have a profile picture then the profile picture of the user serves as the user’s symbol and if the user does not have a profile picture then a default icon serves as the user’s symbol.\n\n6. The striking feature of this game is that the computer is intelligent. If it is the computer's turn and if the computer is winning in any row, column or diagonal, then the computer will place its symbol at a location on tic-tac-toe board such that by placing it's symbol at that location it (i.e the computer) wins the game.\nIf it is computer's turn and if there are multiple locations on tic-tac-toe board at which if the computer places it's symbol then it wins,then in that case, the computer will choose one of the positions to place it's symbol and then the computer will place it's symbol at that location and it will win the game.\nIf it is the computer's turn and if the player is winning in any row, column or diagonal, then the computer will place its symbol at a location on tic tac toe board such that by placing it's symbol at that location it (i.e the computer) stops the player from winning.\nIf it is the computer's turn and if there are multiple locations on tic-tac-toe board at which if the player places his/her symbol then he/she wins, then in that case the computer will choose one of the positions to place it's symbol.\nThe first priority of the computer is to win and the second priority of the computer is to stop the player from winning.\nIf a case arises that it is the computer's turn and both the computer and the player are winning, then, the computer will place its symbol at a location on tic-tac-toe board such that by placing it's symbol at that location it (i.e the computer) wins the game,since the first priority of computer is to win the game and second priority is to stop player from winning.\nIf it is the computer's turn and if neither the player nor the computer are winning, then the computer places its symbol at one of the empty locations on the tic-tac-toe board.\n\n7. When signed in, users can choose to play multiplayer games by sending invitations to specific players. When the invitee accepts the invitation, a real time-multiplayer game is created between the invitee and the host and the two players can then play an online real time multiplayer game.\n\n\n8. In the online multiplayer game,the host has the first turn.\n\n9. In the online multiplayer game, if the host has a profile picture, then the profile picture of the host serves as the host’s symbol, else the symbol ‘X’ serves as the host’s symbol. If the invitee has a profile picture, then the profile picture of the invitee serves as the invitee’s symbol,else the symbol ‘O’ serves as the invitee’s symbol.\n\n10. During the online multiplayer game, the back buttons of android devices of both players are disbaled so that the players don’t terminate the game while the game is being played\n\n11. At the end of the online multiplayer game, the two players are presented with the result of the game. The invitee has the option to play the game again. The host has the option to play again or cancel the game, if the host cancels the game, then the game ends and both the players are redirected to the main activity.\n\n12. When signed in, users can view the invitations sent to them.\n\n13. Users have the option to either accept or reject an invitation.\n\n14. When an invitee accepts an invitation, the invitation is deleted.\n\n15. When signed in, users can edit their profile picture and/or username.\n\n16. Users can update their profile picture by selecting a picture from the device.\n\n 17.Statistics are only saved when users play games while signed in.\n\n18. When signed in, users can view their profile which consists of username,email and profile picture.\n\n19. When signed in,users can view their statistics.\n\n20. When signed in, users may choose to reset their stats (set all of their stats back to initial value, i.e set number of games won,number of games lost, etc back to 0).\n\n21. When users click on ‘reset stats’, a dialogue box appears asking them to confirm whether or not they want to reset the stats. If they click ‘Yes’, then their stats are reset.  If they click ‘No’, then their stats are not reset.\n\n22. Users can reset their password by receiving a password reset email.\n\n23. Users can also play without signing in but then the statistics of the games played will not be saved. \n\n24. When users are not signed in, they can play either in single-player mode or in multiplayer mode. \n\n25. In single-player mode, users choose their symbol (X or O,If the user chooses ‘X’, then the computer gets the symbol ‘O’ and vice-versa) and turn choice (whether the user should start the game or the computer should start the game) and then the users plays against the intelligent computer (the features of which have already been described earlier).\n\n26. In multiplayer mode, two players enter their names and choose their symbols. The two players cannot have the same symbol. The player whose name is entered under the editable text “player 1’s name” begins the game. The two players play on the same device.\n\n27. At the end of single player and multiplayer games,users can choose to play again with the same details (user symbol, turn choice,etc) or return to the main activity.\n\n28. When signed in, playing of games, resetting of stats,etc is only possible if the device has an active internet connection (i.e. wifi or mobile network),thus, if users wish to play game,reset their stats,etc while signed in,then it is checked whether or not they have an active internet connection (i.e. wifi or mobile network), if not, then they are told that internet access is not available, if they do have an internet connection then they proceed with game,resetting of stats,etc."
            android:textAppearance="@style/TextAppearance.AppCompat.Body2"
            android:textColor="@color/black"
            android:textSize="18sp" />
    </ScrollView>

</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>